So I just finished listening to Amanda Seale's radio show on KBLA 1580.
Go and download Travis Smiley Talk Show.
And, you know, we always talk about how we are experiencing heavy censoring throughout all kinds of media, social platforms, television, movies, and radio shows.
And so to have Amanda Seale's uncensored, talking about the real issues of community, not tied to Democrats or Republicans, not tied to an agenda.
And I really appreciate her.
And I think this is huge news and everybody needs to go and download this app, KBLA 1580.
Go and follow Amanda.
It's Fridays at Pacific Standard Time, 12 to 2.
They're based here in Inglewood, California, 12 to 2 and 4 to 6.
So I was just in the car listening to the show and, you know, I'm just we need more of this.
You need to go and download the app.
Listen to Amanda, who talks about the real issues.
And so super appreciative.
But just want to let you know, in case you are not aware, we need more platforms like this.
Who are willing to put people, independent journalists, local artists and give them a voice.